http://www.wmma.org/policy.cfm

Member Benefits
Membership Eligibility Requirements (MERs)
Privacy Statement
The Wood Machinery Manufacturers of America (WMMA) values your privacy and the following privacy statement covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by WMMA when you visit our website or when you purchase WMMA products and services online. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information.
Information Collection
WMMA collects personal information in order to deliver a superior level of customer service. In order to facilitate online transactions and allow user access to Members-Only features, WMMA collects certain information such as names, addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, membership IDS, and credit card numbers. In addition, your personal information helps us to keep you posted on the latest meetings, products, and events that you might like to hear about.
The WMMA website requires you to provide personally identifiable information in order to use certain functions of the site. By providing such information, you consent to WMMA's collection and use of it, as described in this Privacy Statement.
The information you provide may include information collected during the registration process, including contact information (name, address, phone number, e-mail address, dietary restrictions, website urls and titles) and financial information (credit card number). This information will be used to process your order and, if necessary, to contact you regarding the status of your order.
We may provide limited personal information to the following trusted providers to enhance our membership services and for the benefit of our members:
Survey Monkey, Crowd Compass, Magnet Mail, Constant Contact, Doodle, Lebovic Communications (online partners)
Potomac Digitek (hosting partner)
Abila (AMS provider)
WMMA understand the importance of minimizing the amount of Personal Identifiable Information (PII) data it maintains and retains such date only as long as necessary. We maintain organizational record retention procedures, which dictate the length of date retention to meet business, legal and operational needs.
WMMA will not ask your permission to collect or use aggregate information about website visitors or users of our products and services, since aggregate data does not identify you as a specific individual.
Information Disclosure
WMMA takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that WMMA does not sell or rent your e-mail address to other companies. To help us provide superior service, we may share personal information with credit card processing companies, merchants, and any other third party that may need the information for your request to be processed. These organizations have their own privacy and collection practices, and WMMA is not responsible for their independent policies. At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.
How to Opt-Out of WMMA Electronic Communications
We may from time to time send you information about our programs, products, and services via e-mail messages. If you no longer wish to receive our e-mail newsletter or promotional messages, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in the e-mail message or contact kristin@wmma.org.
Use of Cookies
Like many websites, WMMA.org uses "cookies" and other technologies to help us understand which parts of the website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.
If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to disable or enable the cookie feature. Please note that cookies may be necessary to enable you to use certain features on our website.
Links
The WMMA website contains links to other sites. WMMA is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on our website.
Information Security
WMMA will take every precaution to protect your personal information. All personal information collected on individuals will be kept confidential and in a secure environment. Access to personal information will be restricted to only those personnel with a legitimate business purpose.
Contact Us
By joining WMMA and consenting on this privacy policy you are giving us permission to process your personal data for membership services in WMMA and for purposes outline above. You may withdraw consent at any time, or correct or update any of the information you provide to us at any time by sending an e-mail to kristin@WMMA.org, or by calling (443) 640-1052.
WMMA welcomes your comments and questions about the website, your experience with our site and services, and our Privacy Policy.
Woodworking Industry Conference (WIC19)
Membership Eligibility Requirements (MERs)
2331 Rock Spring Road, Forest Hill, MD 21050   –   Phone (443) 640-1052   –   Fax (443) 640-1031   –   Email: info@wmma.org
Terms of Use   –
Privacy Policy   –
Site Map
